[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "RB", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 39, "question": "What is it like to be actually there?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "it", "like", "to", "be", "actually", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 40, "answer": "Well, Piers, it's unbelievable and I think appalling, as you said, is a good word and also war zone, as well.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "Piers", ",", "it", "'s", "unbelievable", "and", "I", "think", "appalling", ",", "as", "you", "said", ",", "is", "a", "good", "word", "and", "also", "war", "zone", ",", "as", "well", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 71, "question": "I mean what is the state of the emergency rescue operation?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "what", "is", "the", "state", "of", "the", "emergency", "rescue", "operation", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 72, "answer": "Well, they think everyone is accounted for.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "they", "think", "everyone", "is", "accounted", "for", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 84, "question": "Where does this rank in terms of size and power and I suppose more pertinently what is happening tonight and which areas are most in danger?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "does", "this", "rank", "in", "terms", "of", "size", "and", "power", "and", "I", "suppose", "more", "pertinently", "what", "is", "happening", "tonight", "and", "which", "areas", "are", "most", "in", "danger", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "RB", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "NN", "CC", "WDT", "NNS", "VBP", "JJS", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 85, "answer": "I'll start with the first one.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ll", "start", "with", "the", "first", "one", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 114, "question": "I know your home has just been wiped away, right?", "question_tokens": ["I", "know", "your", "home", "has", "just", "been", "wiped", "away", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "VBN", "RB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 115, "answer": "Yes, sir, my home was destroyed, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "sir", ",", "my", "home", "was", "destroyed", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["5:00 this morning"]}, "docId": "120229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "CC", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "CD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 117, "question": "Obviously devastating for you and your family but do you feel lucky to be alive?", "question_tokens": ["Obviously", "devastating", "for", "you", "and", "your", "family", "but", "do", "you", "feel", "lucky", "to", "be", "alive", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 118, "answer": "We're very lucky to be alive and just a good disaster plan at home and well executed at 5:00 this morning.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "'re", "very", "lucky", "to", "be", "alive", "and", "just", "a", "good", "disaster", "plan", "at", "home", "and", "well", "executed", "at", "5:00", "this", "morning", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VB", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "DT", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", "RP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "EX", "VBD", "NN", "NN", "IN", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 122, "question": "Can you tell me what it was like when you realized what was happening?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "tell", "me", "what", "it", "was", "like", "when", "you", "realized", "what", "was", "happening", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "WP", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 123, "answer": "We were asleep -- well, we woke up half the roof was coming off the house and we managed to get the small children in the -- in the closet and about the time the small children were in the closet my wife and I noticed the walls separating from the house and it wasn't just a couple seconds later it was quiet and it was -- it was very obvious there was utter devastation around there.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "were", "asleep", "--", "well", ",", "we", "woke", "up", "half", "the", "roof", "was", "coming", "off", "the", "house", "and", "we", "managed", "to", "get", "the", "small", "children", "in", "the", "--", "in", "the", "closet", "and", "about", "the", "time", "the", "small", "children", "were", "in", "the", "closet", "my", "wife", "and", "I", "noticed", "the", "walls", "separating", "from", "the", "house", "and", "it", "was", "n't", "just", "a", "couple", "seconds", "later", "it", "was", "quiet", "and", "it", "was", "--", "it", "was", "very", "obvious", "there", "was", "utter", "devastation", "around", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "JJR", "IN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 125, "question": "ORGAN: Yes, I mean, is there anything more -- is there anything more that the people of the town could have done, do you think, or is it just one of those things when everyone is asleep and you just have to deal with what happens?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "Yes", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "is", "there", "anything", "more", "--", "is", "there", "anything", "more", "that", "the", "people", "of", "the", "town", "could", "have", "done", ",", "do", "you", "think", ",", "or", "is", "it", "just", "one", "of", "those", "things", "when", "everyone", "is", "asleep", "and", "you", "just", "have", "to", "deal", "with", "what", "happens", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNPS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "EX", "NN", "JJR", ":", "VBZ", "RB", "NN", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WRB", "NN", "VBZ", "VB", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "WP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 126, "answer": "You know, I watched it earlier on, and it didn't seem that bad on the news forecast and the weather forecast.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "watched", "it", "earlier", "on", ",", "and", "it", "did", "n't", "seem", "that", "bad", "on", "the", "news", "forecast", "and", "the", "weather", "forecast", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["today"]}, "docId": "120229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "WP", "VBD", "VBN", "VBN", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 156, "question": "Mr. Hicks, did you know people who had been hurt?", "question_tokens": ["Mr.", "Hicks", ",", "did", "you", "know", "people", "who", "had", "been", "hurt", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "WP", "VBD", "VBN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 157, "answer": "Yes, we knew people who had been hurt today and injured in our town, yes, we did.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "we", "knew", "people", "who", "had", "been", "hurt", "today", "and", "injured", "in", "our", "town", ",", "yes", ",", "we", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Hicks"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NN", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "IN", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "IN", "RB", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 166, "question": "Where will you be spending this evening, and what are your plans in the immediate near future for where you and your family will live?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "will", "you", "be", "spending", "this", "evening", ",", "and", "what", "are", "your", "plans", "in", "the", "immediate", "near", "future", "for", "where", "you", "and", "your", "family", "will", "live", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "JJ", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 167, "answer": "We've got insurance companies will be in here the next 48 hours and for right now a local church and a couple of other organizations put us in a motel room for the night so we're pretty fortunate tonight.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "'ve", "got", "insurance", "companies", "will", "be", "in", "here", "the", "next", "48", "hours", "and", "for", "right", "now", "a", "local", "church", "and", "a", "couple", "of", "other", "organizations", "put", "us", "in", "a", "motel", "room", "for", "the", "night", "so", "we", "'re", "pretty", "fortunate", "tonight", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["this evening"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ":", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "RP", "CC", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 236, "question": "And how far had it gone?", "question_tokens": ["And", "how", "far", "had", "it", "gone", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 237, "answer": "It's -- there's an apartment building about 15 feet away from it and it had picked the trailer up and thrown it against the apartment building.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "--", "there", "'s", "an", "apartment", "building", "about", "15", "feet", "away", "from", "it", "and", "it", "had", "picked", "the", "trailer", "up", "and", "thrown", "it", "against", "the", "apartment", "building", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"], "TIME": ["this evening"]}, "docId": "120229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 254, "question": "What are your immediate actions to try and bring the town back under I guess some form of order?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "your", "immediate", "actions", "to", "try", "and", "bring", "the", "town", "back", "under", "I", "guess", "some", "form", "of", "order", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 255, "answer": "Well, Piers, thank you so much for having us on this evening, first of all.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "Piers", ",", "thank", "you", "so", "much", "for", "having", "us", "on", "this", "evening", ",", "first", "of", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["this morning"]}, "docId": "120229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBN", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 296, "question": "How did you hear the news?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "hear", "the", "news", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 297, "answer": "My wife called me this morning.", "answer_tokens": ["My", "wife", "called", "me", "this", "morning", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 302, "question": "Were you good friends?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "you", "good", "friends", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 303, "answer": "Well, yes, we were quite good friends.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "yes", ",", "we", "were", "quite", "good", "friends", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 332, "question": "Was he content with his life, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "he", "content", "with", "his", "life", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 333, "answer": "Oh, I think so, absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "I", "think", "so", ",", "absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 356, "question": "When was the last time you spoke to him, Micky?", "question_tokens": ["When", "was", "the", "last", "time", "you", "spoke", "to", "him", ",", "Micky", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 357, "answer": "It would have been just a few months ago.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "would", "have", "been", "just", "a", "few", "months", "ago", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Micky"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBD", ":", "VBD", "PDT", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 370, "question": "Did that bring Davy a lot of pleasure, the fact that you guys were back together and getting great reviews and so on?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "that", "bring", "Davy", "a", "lot", "of", "pleasure", ",", "the", "fact", "that", "you", "guys", "were", "back", "together", "and", "getting", "great", "reviews", "and", "so", "on", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "VBG", "NNP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "CC", "VBG", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 371, "answer": "Always did -- did all of us, yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Always", "did", "--", "did", "all", "of", "us", ",", "yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Davy"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 414, "question": "What do you want me to do?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "want", "me", "to", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 415, "answer": "One of your quick little things.", "answer_tokens": ["One", "of", "your", "quick", "little", "things", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 418, "question": "What?", "question_tokens": ["What", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "."], "aSentId": 419, "answer": "I really think you should have been a jockey.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "really", "think", "you", "should", "have", "been", "a", "jockey", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 432, "question": "Did he remain proud of his English roots, Micky?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "he", "remain", "proud", "of", "his", "English", "roots", ",", "Micky", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NNP", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 433, "answer": "Oh, absolutely, he had family back there.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "absolutely", ",", "he", "had", "family", "back", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Micky"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 443, "question": "When you're hearing all the tributes today, Micky, and all the music being played again and so on, what's your abiding memory of Davy Jones?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "'re", "hearing", "all", "the", "tributes", "today", ",", "Micky", ",", "and", "all", "the", "music", "being", "played", "again", "and", "so", "on", ",", "what", "'s", "your", "abiding", "memory", "of", "Davy", "Jones", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "CC", "DT", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "VBN", "RB", "CC", "RB", "IN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 444, "answer": "Oh, boy, it's a lot.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "boy", ",", "it", "'s", "a", "lot", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Micky", "Davy Jones"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 492, "question": "When you think about the whole campaign so far, what do you think internally have been the issues that you've had to really confront that are the most pertinent?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "think", "about", "the", "whole", "campaign", "so", "far", ",", "what", "do", "you", "think", "internally", "have", "been", "the", "issues", "that", "you", "'ve", "had", "to", "really", "confront", "that", "are", "the", "most", "pertinent", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "RB", "VB", "IN", "VBP", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 493, "answer": "Well, this is a very competitive field.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "this", "is", "a", "very", "competitive", "field", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Tuesday"]}, "docId": "120229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBP", "VBN", "NNS", "IN", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 514, "question": "How many do you realistically think you can win on the night?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "do", "you", "realistically", "think", "you", "can", "win", "on", "the", "night", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 515, "answer": "Well, there are ten states that are going to be voting on Tuesday.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "there", "are", "ten", "states", "that", "are", "going", "to", "be", "voting", "on", "Tuesday", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["night"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 527, "question": "Do you -- are you seeing a guy who is itching to get on to the main event?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "--", "are", "you", "seeing", "a", "guy", "who", "is", "itching", "to", "get", "on", "to", "the", "main", "event", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 528, "answer": "One thing about our campaign is that we're not taking anything for granted.", "answer_tokens": ["One", "thing", "about", "our", "campaign", "is", "that", "we", "'re", "not", "taking", "anything", "for", "granted", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 561, "question": "Am I right?", "question_tokens": ["Am", "I", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 562, "answer": "I would totally agree with you that we just haven't had the winter weather and that big punch of heavy snow storms that we saw last year.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "totally", "agree", "with", "you", "that", "we", "just", "have", "n't", "had", "the", "winter", "weather", "and", "that", "big", "punch", "of", "heavy", "snow", "storms", "that", "we", "saw", "last", "year", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120229pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", ",", "DT", "NN", "DT", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", ":", "DT", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CD", ",", "RB", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 575, "question": "They don't hit directly on small towns, do they?", "question_tokens": ["They", "do", "n't", "hit", "directly", "on", "small", "towns", ",", "do", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 576, "answer": "Well, I will tell you, the way this goes with this -- this is, you know, 15, maybe 20 tornadoes in a cycle -- is not an incredibly bizarre pattern.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "will", "tell", "you", ",", "the", "way", "this", "goes", "with", "this", "--", "this", "is", ",", "you", "know", ",", "15", ",", "maybe", "20", "tornadoes", "in", "a", "cycle", "--", "is", "not", "an", "incredibly", "bizarre", "pattern", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]